Samuel Hsu

Location: Austin, TX 78705 | Phone: (361) 827-1818 | Email: sky19930112@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/samuel-hsu-b9a73b241/

Github: https://github.com/sky19930112

Portfolio: https://sky19930112.github.io/PortfolioWithReact/

Full Stack Web Developer who recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development Program from The Coding Boot Camp at UT Austin. Expertise in MERN stack, MVC stack, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, NoSQL, React.js, PWA, JavaScript, CSS, and HTML. Experienced deploying via git bash to GitHub and Heroku. A penchant problem solver who can search and figure out how to identify the problem and find solutions to achieve the goal.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, Python3, MySQL, NoSQL(MongoDB)

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Heroku,

Tools: Express.js, Node, Handlebars, Query, Bootstrap, React

Frameworks: React, Handlebars

Core Concepts: MERN Stack, Model-View-Controller(MVC),

PROJECTS

WeatherBoard

| Github: https://github.com/sky19930112/WeatherBoard

| Deployed Project : https://sky19930112.github.io/WeatherBoard

- This web-app is able to search the weather of the city
- Developer: Sole author; main subject for this project is usage of API
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, 3rd party API

Lechonks-Larder

| Github: https://github.com/ParksFG/Lechonks-Larder | Deployed: https://lechonks-larder.herokuapp.com

- set up accounts and info of the pokemon cards; then let the users able to contact each other then do the trading
- Back-end Developer: apollo and graphql for the server set up
- MERN stack, MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, Javascript, GraphQL, Apollo, Heroku, GitHub

RecipelO

| Github: https://github.com/Lawhornmatt/RecipelO

| Deployed: https://recipeio-project2.herokuapp.com/login

- set up account and make own recipes and search for recipes
- front-end Developer: focus on front-end functions with javascript
- MVC stack, Javascript, handlebars, Express, node, MySQL,

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023

Walmart - Associate

Austin, TX 78757, United States

Communicated effectively with leadership, sense of co-working and help out colleagues

April 2022 - November 2022

Elemental Woodwork - Woodworker

Austin, TX 78728, United States

accomplish client's needs

Keep eyes on working environments improvements

Plan ahead for projects

Dec 2021 - May 2022

Mythic Guitar Company - Guitar repair tech

Austin, TX 78728, United States

Troubleshooting the issues

Communicate with clients and leader about solutions

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Team-member, Amazon, San Marcos, Texas EMT on ambulance, Pingtung County Fire Department, Pingtung city, Taiwan Guitar instructor, Austin, Texas

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: The University of Texas at Austin (Center for

Professional Education), Austin, Texas

Jazz Music bachelor's degree: Texas State University, San Marcos, Texas